# **MAYUR BHATIA**

(774) 274-1615 mayurbhatia47@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a versatile sales professional with 8+ years in client-facing roles and hands-on experience with various direct and digital marketing channels. I have made key contributions in the implementations and design of marketing systems, strategies and content. I excel at analytical and creative problem-solving and maintain a reliable history of driving solutions and delivering projects on schedule.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

## Full-Stack Developer/Teaching Asst.

## **Coding Temple**

July 2018 - Present

- Delivered various full-stack web applications using Python, Flask, React.js and SQL on schedule.
- Developed E-commerce web applications with a secure back-end to handle financial transactions.
- Wireframed projects, designed templates and turned them into responsive, mobile optimized apps.
- Used Python NumPy, SciPy and Pandas packages to perform dataset manipulation and statistical analysis.
- Handled data migration between sources and composed complex queries on SQL to extract data from relational databases.
- Assisted with student queries, questions, errors and presentations in class and during live coding sessions.

## **Senior Sales and Rental Agent**

## **East Coast Realty**

Jan 2019 - Present

- Signed and cultivated exclusive client relationships by consistently delivering above expectations with quick turnover times and returns 5-10% above comparable market offerings.
- Negotiated 60 or more complex contracts annually in a dynamic, fast-paced marketplace.
- Averaged 10 new listing acquisitions monthly and created attractive marketing materials paired with quality photos, while ensuring the enhancement of present inventory.
- Tripled the company's online reach and presence by adding a social media presence on Google, LinkedIn and Facebook.
- Led new agent sign ups and onboarding along with accompanied field visits with customers.

## Senior Sales and Rental Agent

## **Cambridge Premier Realty, LLC**

Dec 2016 - Jan 2019

- Generated and qualified about 400 leads a month through direct and digital marketing platforms.
- Increased repeat business opportunities and retention rates by offering exceptional customer service.
- Researched local markets conditions, forecast demand and comparative analysis using technology platform.

# **Sales Support Manager**

# MCM Imports, LLC

Feb 2015 - Jun 2015

- Improved lead generation by 20-30% by implementing a rewards system for client referrals.
- Bi-weekly participation at local wine society events of 40+ attendees to raise brand awareness.
- Closed about 4 new accounts monthly with effective marketing and sales presentations.
- Resolved client invoicing and account issues with 96% success rate.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Providence, RI

## **Johnson & Wales University**

May 2012

• B.S in Entrepreneurship and Marketing (GPA: 3.67)

## **CERTIFICATIONS AND TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Licensed Real Estate Salesperson, Massachusetts (Nov 2015 Present).
- Proficiency in Office Suite, G-Suite, Customer Relationship Management and Point of Sale systems.
- Real Estate photography, ad syndication and database management.
- Full-stack website development, deployment, hosting and management.
- Direct, social media and affiliate marketing strategy and execution.
- Native level speaker in English and Hindi.